giftofspeed.com 2015-03-16

# Privacy Policy

GiftOfSpeed is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of the www.giftofspeed.com site. By accessing the site, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy statement.

**Collecting Your Personal Information**  
We do not collect any information from our visitors, except for our visitor statistics or when you contact us. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you or allows us to contact you. But we do not store this information either, it is purely used to contact you. Through our web statistics, the Site may collect certain information about your visit, such as the name of the Internet service provider and the Internet Protocol (IP) address through which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the Site; the pages that you access while at the Site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. This information is used for the operation and improvement of the Site.

**Use of Your Personal Information**  
We do not collect any personal information except for your I.P. number through our visitor statistics.  
GiftOfSpeed may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on GiftOfSpeed or the Site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of GiftOfSpeed and our family of Web sites; or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of GiftOfSpeed employees or agents, users of GiftOfSpeed products or services, or members of the public.

**Control of Your Personal Information**  
Except as otherwise described in this statement, personal information you provide on the Site will not be shared outside of GiftOfSpeed without your permission.

Please be aware that this privacy statement and any choices you make on the Site will not necessarily apply to personal information you may have provided to GiftOfSpeed in the context of other, separately operated, GiftOfSpeed products or services.

**Cookies**  
We don’t use any cookies on this Site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server.

**Changes to This Privacy Statement**  
We may occasionally update this privacy statement. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

**Contact Information**  
GiftOfSpeed welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you believe that GiftOfSpeed has not adhered to this privacy statement, please [contact us](http://www.giftofspeed.com/contact/) and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
